nakedfunny.com 2010-09-24

# Privacy Policy - Naked and Funny NakedFunny.Com

**Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated: 24.08.09  **

At AFL Productions, LLC ("AFL"), we respect your right to privacy and we understand that members and visitors to AFL need to control the uses of their personal information. The privacy policy below details the measures taken by AFL to protect your privacy in connection with your use of _[www.nakedfunny.com](http://www.nakedfunny.com/)_ or any successor(s) thereto and/or assigns thereof (AFL Site(s)). However, AFL's service is designed to allow users to post photographs and information about themselves. Accordingly, by submitting your photograph and/or any personal information, you thereby waive any privacy expectations you have with respect to our use of your likeness or personal information provided to us. If you do not wish to have your picture or information about yourself viewed by or disclosed to others, do not use our service.

By using AFL Site(s), you affirmatively consent to this Privacy Policy and agree to have your personal information (to the extent voluntarily disclosed by you) collected by AFL (or its agents or contractors) and transferred to and processed in the United States.

**Information Collection and Use**

AFL collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the AFL service. AFL also collects other data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other and making content recommendation.

AFL also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. We may use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. 

From time to time, AFL or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on the AFL Site(s). Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply.

**Use of Cookies**

AFL uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you must enable cookies from AFL in order to use most functions on the site. Please note that AFL allows third party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the AFL Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Advertising**

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by AFL or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by AFL and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Agents**

We use a third party company to pack and ship products ordered in the AFL online store. Our fulfillment company has access to your full name and shipping address to complete this transaction but does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

**Links**

AFL contains links to third-party sites. AFL is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on the AFL Site(s).

**Public Communication**

Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information on the AFL Site(s) that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**

AFL users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account.

**Security**

AFL member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. AFL takes precautions to ensure that member account information is kept private. We use commercially reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. When members submit their personal information or log into their accounts on AFL.com, the information transmitted is protected by industry standard encryption. For any additional information about the security measures we use on AFL, please send us a message via the _Contact_ page. However, we do not guarantee that these efforts will completely protect member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. We will endeavor to notify members in the event that the security of their personal information is breached or compromised. By submitting personal information on our AFL Site(s), you expressly consent to receiving our notification regarding any breach or compromise, or suspected breach or compromise, of the security of your personal information, by email or postal mail, as we deem appropriate, and as required by law.

We urge you to keep your username, password, and other account access information in a safe place and not to divulge it to anyone. Also, remember to sign off your account and close your browser window when you have finished your visit. This is to ensure that others cannot access your account, especially if you are sharing a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place such as a library or an internet cafe.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information AFL Collects**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, AFL will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to comply with applicable law or to respond to a subpoena, court order, search warrant or other legal process received by AFL, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of a third party; (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service; or (4) to respond to an emergency. AFL reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of AFL or substantially all of AFL’s assets to that successor in interest. AFL also reserves the right to disclose personal information as necessary to enable third-party service providers to support and maintain the operation of AFL.com and AFL’s service. You will be notified via e-mail of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below.

**Children's Privacy**

AFL is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests. AFL Site(s) and AFL’s service are not intended for and may not be used by children under the age of 13. AFL does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and does not target its website or service to children under 13.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is subject to change by AFL from time to time. If we make changes, we will post the changes on our AFL Site(s) and/or notify members via email. Also, we may ask members to review and consent to the changes at the time of their next account log-in. By continuing to use our AFL Site(s) after such notice and consent, members agree to be bound by the changes to this Privacy Policy.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this AFL Site(s), please send us a message via the _Contact_ page (or via mail: AFL Productions, LLC, Attn: [volax@netwiz.net](mailto:volax@netwiz.net) ).

**California Privacy Rights**

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of AFL who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send us a message via the _Contact_ page or write us at: AFL Productions, LLC, Attn: nakedfunny@gmail.com .
